<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Top 5 ODI all-rounders</string>


    <string name="c1">Shakib Al Hasan   born 24 March 1987) is a Bangladeshi international cricketer who holds the record for being ranked first as an all rounder in the One Day International (ODI) format for 10 years and is still among the top 3 in highest current rankings in all three formats of the game (Test, T20I and ODIs).[1][2][3] He was ranked as one of the world s most famous athletes by ESPN WORLD FAME 100 in 2019. His aggressive left-handed batting style in the middle order, controlled slow left-arm orthodox bowling, and athletic fielding has helped him win trophies in top leagues across the world.</string>
    <string name="c11">In 2015, Shakib became the first and only cricketer in history to be ranked the No.1 all-rounder by ICC in its Player Rankings in all three formats of the game (Test, Twenty20 and One Day Internationals).[7] He is currently ranked no.1 in odis and no.2 in tests and t-20s. On 13 January 2017, he registered the highest individual score (217) by a Bangladeshi batsman in Tests.[8] In November 2018, he became the first bowler for Bangladesh to take 200 wickets in Tests.[9] In June 2019, Shakib became the fastest player to score 6,000 runs and take 250 wickets in ODIs in just 199 matches.[10] He is the highest run scorer as well as the highest wicket taker for Bangladesh in World Cup. He is also the only cricketer to score 1000 runs and to take 30 wickets in World Cup. At the 2019 Cricket World Cup, Shakib became the first cricketer to score 600 runs and take 10 wickets in a single World Cup.</string>
    <string name="c111">Born in Magura, Khulna, Shakib started playing cricket at an early age. According to Prothom Alo sports editor Utpal Shuvro, Shakib "was fairly proficient at cricket and was often hired to play for different villages and teams".[11] In one of those matches, Shakib impressed an umpire who arranged for him to practice with the Islampur Para Club, a team in the Magura Cricket League. During the practice session, Shakib batted aggressively and bowled fast, as he usually did, but also chose to experiment with spin bowling which proved to be not so effective. He was picked to play for Islampur and took a wicket with his first ball; it was his first delivery with a proper cricket ball, having previously played with a taped tennis ball.[citation needed] He spent six months training at Bangladesh Krira Shiksha Pratisthan,[11] a government-run sports institute.[12] and in 2004, at the age of 17, was drafted by Khulna to play in the National Domestic League.</string>

    <string name="c2">Benjamin Andrew Stokes (born 4 June 1991) is an English international cricketer and current vice-captain of the England Test team. Stokes was part of the England squad that won the 2019 Cricket World Cup.</string>
    <string name="c22">Born in Christchurch, New Zealand, Stokes moved to northern England with his parents at the age of 12,[3] where he learnt the game and began playing club cricket for local teams. He is an all-rounder who bowls right-arm fast-medium pace and bats left-handed.</string>
    <string name="c222">An attacking middle-order batsman, he holds the record for England s fastest ever Test double-century,[5] the fastest ever Test match 250, and the highest ever score for a Test batsman batting at number six. He also holds the record for the most runs scored by an individual batsman in the morning session of a Test match. Stokes became the highest-paid overseas player in the history of the Indian Premier League in 2017, fetching a record contract of ₹145 million ($2,166,604) (£1.7 million); he won the Most Valuable Player award during the season.</string>


    <string name="c3">Mohammad Nabi (Pashto: محمد نبي‎; born 1 January 1985[A]) is an Afghan cricketer who has captained the side in limited overs matches. Nabi is an all-rounder, playing as a right-handed batsman and off break bowler. He played a major role in Afghanistan s rise to the top level of international cricket, playing in both their first One Day International in April 2009 and their first Test match in June 2018. He captained the side during their first appearances in the 2014 Asia Cup and the 2015 Cricket World Cup. Nabi has also played in numerous Twenty20 franchise tournaments and was the first player from Afghanistan to be selected in the Indian Premier League player auction. In September 2019, he announced his retirement from Test cricket to prolong his limited overs cricket career</string>
    <string name="c33">Nabi was born in Logar Province in Afghanistan, but his family moved to Peshawar in Pakistan, fleeing from the Soviet–Afghan War.[5][6] He started playing cricket in Peshawar at the age of 10,[5] and his family moved back to Afghanistan in 2000, where he began playing cricket with Mohammad Shahzad, Asghar Afghan and Shapoor Zadran, all of whom would later become important members of the Afghan national team.[7] Nabi played in his first competitive match in 2003, playing for an Afghanistan team against the Rahim Yar Khan Cricket Association. Afghanistan s team was poor, but Nabi top-scored for the team with 61 runs.[6][8] During this time Afghanistan didn t have their own cricket gear and had to rely on buying it from Pakistan and India.</string>


    <string name="c4">Syed Imad Wasim Haider (Urdu: عماد وسیم‎; born 18 December 1988), commonly known as Imad Wasim, is a Pakistani cricketer who played in the 2006 Under-19 Cricket World Cup for the national team and has also played first-class, List A cricket and Twenty20 cricket in Pakistan.[2] He represented Islamabad Leopards team in Faysal Bank T20 Cup 2012–13 season. He is a left-handed batsman and a left-arm orthodox bowler. He is the current captain of PSL team Karachi Kings.</string>
    <string name="c44">In August 2018, he was one of thirty-three players to be awarded a central contract for the 2018–19 season by the Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB).[3][4] In March 2019, he captained the Pakistan One Day International (ODI) team for the first time.</string>


    <string name="c5">Rashid Khan Arman (Pashto: راشد خان ارمان‎; born 20 September 1998), commonly known as Rashid Khan, is an Afghan cricketer and the current captain of the national team.[1] He was one of the eleven cricketers to play in Afghanistan s first ever Test match, against India, in June 2018. He returned the most expensive bowling figures by a debutant in a nation s maiden Test match.[2] In September 2019, he led the team in the one-off Test against Bangladesh, and at the age of 20 years and 350 days, became the youngest cricketer to captain a Test match side.</string>
    <string name="c55">Rashid played in the 2017 Indian Premier League for Sunrisers Hyderabad. In June 2017, he took the best bowling figures for an associate nation in a One Day International (ODI) match.[4][5] In February 2018, he became the youngest player to top the ICC Player Rankings for bowlers in ODIs.[6] Later the same month, he also topped the ICC Player Rankings for bowlers in T20Is.[7] In September 2018, he became the number one player in the ICC s all-rounder rankings, following his performance at the 2018 Asia Cup.</string>
    <string name="c">In March 2018, during the 2018 Cricket World Cup Qualifier, he captained Afghanistan for the first time in an ODI match. At the age of 19 years and 165 days, he became the youngest player to captain an international side.[9] In the final of the Cricket World Cup Qualifier, against the West Indies, Khan became the fastest and youngest bowler to take 100 wickets in ODIs when he dismissed Shai Hope.[10] He took 44 matches to take his 100th dismissal, breaking the previous record of 52 matches, set by Mitchell Starc of Australia.[10] In June 2018, he became the fastest bowler, in terms of time, to take 50 wickets in T20Is. He reached the milestone in two years and 220 days, in the first T20I against Bangladesh.</string>
</resources>
